And then losing out in the
continuous
enjoyment
The enjoyment of akhirah
Which one will you choose
Will you choose that small
enjoyment and
comfort of this dunya for
hundred years
And then you lose out
You throw away continuous and
everlasting enjoyment
in akhirah
Which one will you choose
That small one in this dunya
That small yacht you are
riding
That small private jet you
are riding
That small house you built in
whether
banana or orange or apple
island
Or you built it in Baytama
and
Asukuru
Or you built it in France,
in Paris, in Argentina,
in Switzerland
You stole the money to do it
The whole of that comfort is
still
small
The whole of that luxury is
still
small
When you compare it to the
luxury
of akhirah
So which one will you prefer
That small one
Throwing away al-khairi daim
Throwing away the one that is
everlasting
The small one that will leave
you
in few years